welcome to the icici prudential family
congratulations on purchasing icici pro
eye protect smart
this is an introductory video guide to
your policy
after going through this short video you
will have a clear understanding of the
benefits which this plan offers and the
things you need to do to ensure that you
get these benefits
let us first start off with the free
look period
to ensure that you are comfortable with
this product we provide you with a
15-day period from the time you received
the policy document to understand the
policy
if you find that there are aspects of
the policy that you are not comfortable
with you can return the policy to us and
you will be eligible for a refund
[Music]
let us now start with the guided tour of
your policy
when applying for your icici pro
iprotect smart policy you would have
made three important choices
the number of years for which you want
the insurance benefit of icici pro i
protect smart
the amount of insurance that you want to
cover yourself for
and whether you would want the insurance
benefit to be paid to your family as a
lump sum or spread over time
these three factors determine your
policy benefits so we request you to go
through your policy kit to ensure that
your policy correctly reflects the
choice you made when applying for it
to get these benefits you only have to
do one thing pay your premiums regularly
year after year
so do make a note of your next premium
due date and pay your premium to ensure
continuous life insurance protection for
you and your loved ones
now let us understand the benefits of
icici brew eye protect smart
icici pro protect smart is a life
insurance policy with a single objective
of providing life insurance cover to the
policy holder
in the unfortunate event of the death of
the person covered by this policy the
life insurance amount will be paid to
the nominee specified by you while
purchasing your policy
there are three ways in which the life
insurance amount can be paid to the
nominee option 1
the nominee gets the entire insurance
amount at one time
option 2
the nominee receives the insurance money
as a monthly income over 10 years
option 3 the nominee receives monthly
income for 10 years with a 10
increase every year
please refer to your policy document to
understand which option you have
selected apart from this there are two
other features of your icici pro i
protect smart policy which you should
make note of
first if the person covered by this
policy has an accident and suffers a
permanent disability the future premiums
of icici pro i protect smart will be
waived off and the benefits of the
policy will continue
second
in a situation where the person covered
by this policy is detected with a
terminal illness the life insurance
amount will be paid to the nominee
[Music]
to summarize the three core features of
icici pro i protect smart are
life insurance amount will be paid out
to the nominee in the unfortunate event
of the death of the person covered by
this policy
in case of permanent disability due to
an accident future premiums will be
waived off and the benefits of the
policy will continue
in case the person covered by this
policy is detected with a terminal
illness the insurance amount will be
paid
[Music]
apart from these core benefits of icici
pro i protect smart there are two
optional benefits which will apply to
policyholders who have opted for these
additional benefits
critical illness cover
today we see and hear about lifestyle
related diseases becoming increasingly
common
it is important that we be prepared for
such situations
under this feature if the person covered
in this policy gets diagnosed with any
of the 34 major illnesses covered in
this plan icici pro i protect smart will
pay the critical illness cover amount to
take care of hospital expenses medical
care expenses and possible loss of
income arising from these diseases
the critical illness cover amount will
be specified in your policy document
accidental death cover
this is yet another optional benefit of
icici pro eye protect smart
in case you have opted for this feature
the next section of the video will be of
interest to you
in case the person covered by this
policy dies due to an accident the
amount paid to the nominee will be two
times of the life insurance amount
do note that both critical illness cover
and accidental death cover are optional
benefits by icici pro eye protect smart
we at icici prudential believe that
every claim represents fulfillment of a
promise made to our policy holders
we are committed towards securing the
future of your loved ones in a manner
that's quick and efficient
in case the policyholder or the nominee
needs to register a claim please write
to claim care at icici brewlife.com
or log in to the claims section of
www.iciciprolife.com
our claim settlement ratio for financial
year 2014 and 2015
is 93.80
we welcome you to the icici prudential
family and look forward to serving you
for a long time for any further queries
about your policy log on to
www.icicipruelife.com
[Music]